very short live and it's going to be very clear and to the point and i'm i'm hoping that some
people will leave this live different than they arrived a question that people ask me on a regular
basis is are there any politicians that you support a question that people ask me on a regular basis
is i mean gosh dang amanda like is there anybody that we can trust in government like you don't
trust nobody and what i need people to understand is that you are still looking at the government as
if it is some source of morality and it never has been would you ask me if i'm looking at a a drug
cartel dang amanda are there any drug dealers you support dang amanda are there any drug dealers that
we can trust no because that makes no sense because the business of selling drugs and narcotics
is 100% sorry i can't even talk grounded rooted in um greed deception and violence
the government is grounded in greed deception and violence for some reason folks keep thinking it is
not even though you were consistently told this on a regular basis you are shown this on a regular
basis you feel it feel it until you are ready to understand that you are run your life
jordi until you are ready to understand that your life as you know it stop is run by corrupt
greedy greedy people you will never do what needs to be done to save yourself you keep thinking that
people are going into politics to do for good for the people even though the the industry because
that's what it is of politics is not built on doing good for the people and it never has been
so it's it's it's it's nonsensical to keep voting and and involving yourself in the propping up of an
establishment that has not been established for your needs all of your effort should be how to
completely dismantle it how to make it crumble to the ground and every time you partake in it
you are keeping it going when it was 2020 and the election and people were like amanda stop telling
people to vote stop people telling to vote for joe biden my whole frustration was you keep telling me
to not vote but you're not telling me what to do on the other side of it so this just feels
disingenuous that's not what i'm doing i'm telling you that it's not about just not voting it's about
taking that energy which is real and that is the other thing that you need to really fully
understand your energy is a real thing it is not some esoteric woo woo made up shit it is actual
energy that is manufactured energy that is utilized into other things so when you are putting your
energy into this direction and it is being turned over and processed and applied to shit that doesn't
apply to you you are harming yourself your energy needs to be put in this direction to creating systems
to creating infrastructures to creating organization that supports you while undermining them
it's twofold the problem with so many organizations is that they seek to support you while still having to be
attached to them our energy our thinkers in here our innovators in here we need to be thinking how do we
do it different we need to revolutionize what it means to be a revolutionary so the last thing i will say
again is that your continued commitment to thinking that the government is a space of ethics of morals of service
is what's keeping you back you are surprised every time a politician shows themselves to be what they
are you would never be surprised a drug dealer would show themselves to be who they are never you're like
yeah that's what's required in this business it would require you in the drug dealing business to
murder people it would require you in the drug dealing business to lie it would require you in the drug
dealing business to stab people in the back because it is a corrupt greedy business that is the exact
same business as politics it is a corrupt greedy violent business that requires the exact same behaviors
as all of the spaces that you have been told are filled with terrible people
stop aligning stop assigning these people a credibility that they do not deserve my new album
truth translator comes out june 14th if you want more conversations like this please
subscribe to my patreon have a good one y'all
you